BUT WHAT STANDS IN THEIR POWER.
YEARS AFTER THE 2016 ELECTION,
FORMER OBAMA CIA CHIEF JOHN
BRENNAN WAS UNAMBIGUOUS.
INTERVIEW AFTER INTERVIEW, HE
TOLD US THE STEELE DOSSIER
PLAYED NO ROLE IN THE CIA'S
INTELLIGENCE ASSESSMENT OF
RUSSIAN INTERFERENCE IN THE 2016
ELECTION.
BRENNAN BY THE WAY TOLD THIS
UNDER OATH.
THE IG REPORT INDICATES THAT HE
WAS LYING.
LYING.
BY STATEMENTS THAT ATTRACTED THE
INTEREST OF U.S. ATTORNEY JOHN
DURHAM.
JOHN KIRK WHO IS INTERESTED,
HE'S A FORMER CIA OFFICER AND
THE WHISTLE-BLOWER WHO WENT
TO JAIL FOR DOING LESS THAN
JOHN BRENNAN HAS DONE.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> Tucker: YOU SOMEONE WHOSE
LIFE WAS TURNED THE BULLY UPSIDE
DOWN, DESTROYED FOR A WHILE SEEN
DOWN, DESTROYED FOR A WHILE SEEG
DOWN, DESTROYED FOR A WHILE SEEA
GUY LIKE BRENNAN COMMIT PERJURY
IN PUBLIC AND NOBODY CARES, HOW
DOES THAT MAKE YOU FEEL?
>> THAT SEEMS TO BE WHAT WE ARE
SEEING NOW.
IF "THE NEW YORK TIMES" IS TO BE
BELIEVED, JOHN BRENNAN WAS
SAYING ONE THING ON CAPITOL HILL
AND MSNBC WHERE HE IS A PAID
TALKING HEAD AND ANOTHER THING
INTERNALLY TO HIS OWN PEOPLE AND
JIM COMEY, WHO WAS FBI DIRECTOR
AT THE TIME.
WE KNOW THAT JOHN DURHAM, THE
U.S. ATTORNEY FOR THE STATE OF
CONNECTICUT WHO IS DOING THIS
INVESTIGATION HAS NOW ASKED FOR
AND WILL RECEIVE CALL LOGS FROM
JOHN BRENNAN, EMAILS FROM JOHN
BRENNAN FROM THE TIME THAT HE
WAS THE CIA DIRECTOR, AS WELL AS
CONTEMPORANEOUS NOTES THAT
BRENNAN TOOK WHEN HE WAS MEETING
WITH THESE OTHER LEADERS.
WE ARE LOOKING AT ONE OF THESE
ARE MANY OF THESE PROCESS
CRIMES, MAKING A FALSE
STATEMENT, PERJURY, WHICH SEEMS
TO BE WHAT JOHN DURHAM IS
PICKING UP.
A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO, JOHN
DURHAM SAID THAT HIS
INVESTIGATION IS NOT AN INJURY.
IT'S AN INVESTIGATION AND IT'S A
CRIMINAL ONE.
>> Tucker: BRENNAN WOULD'VE
HAVE TO KNOW THIS, CORRECT?
HE WAS AT THE CENTER OF THIS
BEER FOR HIM TO SAY CONFIDENTLY
THE STEELE DOSSIER PLAYED NO
ROLE IN THE FAISAL LAWRENCE, BUT
COMMON SENSE TELLS YOU THAT HE K
COMMON SENSE TELLS YOU THAT HE O
COMMON SENSE TELLS YOU THAT HE S
THIS TO BE UNTRUE AND HE SAID
IT.
>> ABSOLUTELY, JUST LIKE HE
KNOWS THAT THERE WAS NO BUT
HE WASN'T HONEST ABOUT THAT AND
NEITHER WAS JIM COMEY.
WE KNOW HE LIED TO THE FISA
COURT, WE KNOW THEY LIED
MULTIPLE TIMES TO THE FISA COURT
TO GET WARRANTS AGAINST CARTER
PAGE.
I THINK AT THAT LEVEL, WITH
EVERYTHING BEING CLASSIFIED AND
WITH THEIR ARROGANCE AT THE SAME
TIME, I THINK THEY THINK THEY
CAN JUST GET AWAY WITH IT.
THE TRUTH ISN'T GOING TO COME
OUT IN THE END.
IT LOOKS LIKE IT WILL COME OUT.
THE ONE I WANT THEM BECAUSE I
LOVE THE COUNTRY AND I WANT TO
BELIEVE IN OUR JUSTICE SYSTEM.
YOU SEE ROGER STONE IN EFFECT
FACING LIFE IN PRISON.
YOU SEE THE WHISTLE-BLOWER
VENERATED AS A CHRIST FIGURE.
YOU ARE A LEGITIMATE
WHISTLE-BLOWER AND YOU GO TO
JAIL.
YOU GOT TO WONDER IS THIS ON THE
LEVEL?
>> I WAS TALKING THIS WITH MY
CHILDREN THE OTHER DAY AND THEY
ASK ESSENTIALLY THE SAME
QUESTION FOR THEY SAY, WHEN I
WAS GROWING UP, I ALWAYS ASSUMED
ADULTS WERE SMARTER THAN KIDS
AND ADULTS WERE FAIR BECAUSE
THERE WERE ADULTS, WE ALL COME
TO REALIZE IT.
THAT'S SIMPLY NOT TRUE.
PEOPLE HAVE POLITICAL AXES TO
GRIND.
SOMETIMES KARMA IS A REAL THING
AND SOMETIMES THERE IS JUSTICE
IN THE END.
>> Tucker: I HAVE NO INSIDE